betfredaffiliates.com 2014-12-31

# Betfred Privacy Policy

The following describes the practices in regards to information gathering and use for the websites operated by Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited (UK) and/or Petfre ( Gibraltar ) Limited, both companies trading as Betfred. These websites include, but are not limited to, www.betfred.com, www.betfredcasino.com, www.betfredpoker.com, www.betfredbingo.com, www.betfredgames.com. 

You agree that both Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited (UK) and Petfre ( Gibraltar ) Limited may hold and process by computer or otherwise any information they hold about you. 

As a customer of Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited and/or Petfre (Gibraltar) Limited, we have a number of obligations to you with regard to the management and processing of your personal information under the Data Protection Act 1998 in the UK and the Data Protection Act 2004 in Gibraltar. This policy sets out the way in which we will deal with the information that you provide to allow us to manage your account efficiently and securely. Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited Data Protection Registration number is Z8005918, and Petfre (Gibraltar) Limited Data Protection Registration number is DP008163.

By using the websites you acknowledge that you have read the terms of this Privacy Policy and that you consent to the use of your information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

Personal information is collected from customers for the following purposes: 

  * the opening, managing and maintaining of accounts; 
  * to help us build up an accurate profile of our client base; 
  * to enable us to carry out statistical and other analysis; 
  * to provide any service to you and contact you with details of promotions, special offers, important service changes, technical updates and changes to terms and conditions and rules; 
  * to verify the accuracy of the information, including disclosure to third parties, such as financial institutions, age verification and credit reporting agencies; 
  * to comply with regulatory duties, obligations and responsibilities under the UK Gambling Act and to the Gambling Commission in the UK in respect of Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited or the Gibraltar Gambling Act 2005 and Gambling Commissioner of Gibraltar in respect of Petfre (Gibraltar) Limited; and 
  * to conform to legal requirements or complying with legal processes or acting to protect the interests of sporting bodies or other qualified bodies. 

We may disclose (and you agree that we may do so) your personal information to any subsidiaries or associated companies and selected third parties with whom we have contractual relationships (including but not limited to suppliers and service providers). You also agree that we may contact you with regard to products, services and related matters which we consider may be of interest to you. We will not send you unsolicited information regarding any third party commercial offers or advertisements. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information is kept securely and protected from unauthorised access. 

If you do not wish to receive promotional information then please use the “opt-out” preference within the My Account section of the website or contact customer services on 0800 032 0878.

You are entitled to a copy of the information we hold about you. If you wish to receive a copy please contact us. We require up to forty (40) days' notice to enable us to comply with such a request. 

We choose partners and associates carefully and our websites contain links to partner sites. Whilst we are confident that these partners comply with privacy laws and regulations, we cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices or content of such partner or associate sites. 

We would recommend you to check and make sure that you have read our most recent policy statement when you visit one of our websites. 

_Updating your information_

You may update or delete your information at any time from within your Betfred account by accessing the My Account section of the website or by contacting customer services on 0800 032 0878.

_Telephone Calls_

Telephone calls to and from our call centre may be recorded for training and security purposes. 

_Cookies_

Transactions carried out on our websites automatically collect information using ‘cookies’. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. 

We use cookies to analyse site usage, improve our content and product offerings and to customise promotional efforts, site content and layout. You can find out more about how Internet sites use cookies on [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

If you prefer, you can turn cookies off in your browser. The ‘Help’ menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive new cookies and how to prevent cookies altogether. If you do turn off or disable cookies, we may be unable to optimise your visit to our site and/or you may not be eligible for certain offers or promotions. 

Our website, its procedures and this policy remain under review and may be updated further in the future. We are not responsible for cookies not controlled by us.

_Overseas transfer of your information_

In connection with the provision of their respective services, Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited and/or Petfre ( Gibraltar ) Limited may need to transfer data (including personal information) to other companies that are not incorporated in the same jurisdiction (and in the case of Done Brothers (Cash Betting) Limited outside the UK ). 

You agree that we may transfer information we hold about you to any country, including countries outside the European Economic Area. 

_Contacting us_

If at any time you believe that we have not adhered to the principles contained within this Privacy Policy, please notify us by email at support@betfred.com and we will use all reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to[ support@betfred.com](mailto:support@betfred.com) or by post to: 

Customer Service Manager   
Betfred   
The Spectrum   
56-58 Benson Road   
Birchwood   
WA3 7PQ
